Guide to the Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the president, 2012-2018; Accession 2019-A-0015
  - Subject Files
    - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transexual and Queer Staff Group - notes, 2014 July 8 (Box 28, Folder 90)
    - Lithuania - Ambassador Visit, 2013 October 30 (Box 28, Folder 91)
    - Long Service Recognition - Dinner, 2013 April 1 (Box 28, Folder 92)
    - Long Service Recognition - Dinner, 2014 March 25 (Box 28, Folder 93)
    - Media - Brazil - Folha de Sao Paulo - Interview Background, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 94)
    - Media - China CCTV with Salovey - Disc, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 95)
    - Media - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Media - Dartmouth Protests - Article, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Media - Fortune Interview, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Media - Huffington Post - Interview - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Media - Nature Television Program - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Media - New Haven Register - Salovey Editorial, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Media - New York Times Subscription, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Media - Online Degree Articles, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Media - Wall Street Journal - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Media - Yale Daily News and Herald, 2015 February 27 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Memorial - Alan Forte, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Memorial - John Hollander, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Memorial - Professor Russett, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Meningitis - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Medical Progress - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Mental Health - Genecin - Meeting Notes, 2015 January 14 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Mental Health - Proposal and Strategy, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Mental Health and Counseling - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Mental Health and Wellness - Initiatives, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Mental Health and Wellness - Weekend, 2013 April 11 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Mentoring - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Mission Statement, 2011-2013 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Mohegan Nation - Book and Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Mory's, 2013-2015 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - National Geographic - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - National Portrait Gallery - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - New Fellow Orientation, 2014 September 17 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - New Haven Indigenous People's Day, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - New Haven Reads, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - New Haven Symphony Orchestra, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Nobel Laureate - Receptions - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Nobel Prize - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Nobel Prize - Ebadi - Visit, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Norfolk - Trustees - Meeting, 2013 April 26 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Norfolk Chamber Music Festival, 2013-2014 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Obituaries - Nuland, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Office of Cooperative Research - Director Soderstrom - Review, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Office of Diversity and Equal Opportunity, 2013-2014 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Office of Institutional Research - Announcements, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Office of Research Administration - Transitions - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - One Yale - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Online Course - Introductory Remarks, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Online Education, 2013-2015 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Online Education - Copyright Policy, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Online Education - Physicians Associates Hybrid Program Summary, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Online Initiatives - Facebook Meeting, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Online Learning, 2012-2013 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Operations Research Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Orthodoxy - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Outreach and Recruitment, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Parents - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Payments in Lieu of Taxes (Pilot) Program Correspondence, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Peck Place School - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Society - Dinner, 2015 February 16 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Phillipines Disaster - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Photographs - Levin and Salovey, c. 2013 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Pipeline and Retention - Third Party Commentary, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Police - Blow Incident - Correspondence, Reports and Statements, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Portrait of Levin - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Prayer - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Prep for Prep - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Post-Baccalaureate Research Education Program (PREP), 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Power Outages - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - President's Reunion Reception, 2014 May 30 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Professors of Bluegrass Band - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Property - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Prospect - New Orleans - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - Psychology Clinic Self-Study Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 68)
    - Public Affairs and Communication - Announcement, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 69)
    - Rankings - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 70)
    - Ratings Agencies, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 71)
    - Recognition - Expanding at Yale, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 72)
    - Recruitment - Koerner - visit, 2014 May 2 (Box 29, Folder 73)
    - Reunion Weekend - Class Sheets and Attendance, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 74)
    - Reunion Weekend - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 75)
    - Yale Russian Chorus - Disc and Correspondence, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 76)
    - Scholars at Risk, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 77)
    - School Students - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 29, Folder 78)
    - School Students - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 79)
    - Schwarzman Scholars, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 80)
    - Science Citadel, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 81)
    - Science, Technology, Engineering and Math (STEM) Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 82)
    - Science, Technology, Engineering and Math (STEM) Teaching - Progress Report, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 83)
    - Security and Fire Safety Annual Report, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 84)
    - Senior Living - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 85)
    - Sex Week - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 29, Folder 86)
    - Sexual Assault - Articles, 2014- 2015 (Box 29, Folder 87)
    - Sexual Misconduct, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 88)
    - Sexual Misconduct - Complaints Report, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 89)
    - Sexual Misconduct - Complaints Report, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 90)
    - Sexual Misconduct - Responses, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 91)
    - Sexual Misconduct - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity Complaint, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 92)
    - Sexual Misconduct - Statistics, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 93)
    - Sexual Misconduct and Title IX - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 29, Folder 94)
    - Sexual Misconduct and Title IX - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 95)
    - Shabtai Jewish Society at Yale - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 96)
    - Shared Services - Notes and Presentation, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 97)
    - Shubert - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 98)
    - Silliman Lectures - Banaji - Introduction, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 99)
    - Singapore - Biographies of Officials, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 100)
    - Singapore - Deputy Minister Shanmaugaratnam - Visit - 14 April, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 101)
    - Singapore - Ministry of Education - Correspondence and Disclosure, 2013-2015 (Box 29, Folder 102)
    - Singapore - Public Service Commission, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 103)
    - Skull and Bones Society - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 104)
    - Smithsonian Institution - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 105)
    - Society of Biblical Literature - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 106)
    - Social Media - Instagram Contest, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 107)
    - Squash Haven - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 108)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parade - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 109)
    - Sterking Fellows- Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Folder 110)
    - Sterling Fellows - Emotional Intelligence Presentation, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 111)
    - Sterling Fellows - Event - 2 May, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 112)
    - Sterling Fellows - Event - 24 April, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 113)
    - Sterling Fellows - Talking Points, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 114)
    - Strengths, Weaknesses, Opportunities, Threats (SWOT) - Notes, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 115)
    - Student Ambassador Program, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 116)
    - Student Debt, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 117)
    - Student Effort, Undated (Box 29, Folder 118)
    - Student Issues - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Student Life, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Student Life - Issues, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Student Life - Reorganizations, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Student Meetings - InGenius Prep, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Student Meetings, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Students - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Style Sheets, 2013-2014 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Summaries of Research, Literature, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Summer Session, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Summer Session - Annual Reports, 2013-2015 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Yale Sustainable Food Project, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Sustainability - Charter Report, 2011-2012 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Sustainability - Correspondence, 2013- 2015 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Sustainability - Initiatives, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Sustainability - Keynote Event, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Sustainability - Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Forum, 2012-2013 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Sustainability - Progress, 2012-2013` (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Sustainability - Strategic Plan, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Sustainability - Yale Alumni Magazine, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Sweatshops - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Swensen Initiative, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Systemic Risk - Article, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Taft School - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Taiwan - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Tanner Lectures, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Tanner Lectures - Annual Meeting, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Tanner Lectures - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Tanner Lectures - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Technology - DeLange Conference, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - TERI Conference, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Terrorism - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Theater Program - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Tibet - Karmapa - Invitations, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Train - One Hour, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Trusteeship, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Turkey - Turkey and Yale, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Tuscany - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - United Kingdom - Prince of Wales Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Ukraine - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - United Way - Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - United Way - Event, 2014 April 22 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - United Way - Meetings, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - U.S. News and World Report - Correspondence and Ranking, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Vaccines - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Valeo Contest - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Visa - Application, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Visiton, Mission, Goals, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Warrior - Scholar Project, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Website - President - Elect, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Wediko School - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - West Campus, 2012-2013 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - West Campus - Dining Room, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - West Campus - Faculty Planning, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - West Campus - Goals and Priorities, 2013-2015 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - West Campus - Strobel, 2013-2015 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - West Campus - Rail System, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - Who's Who Publication - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - Women's Faculty Forum - Annual Report, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - Women's Faculty Forum - Funding and Restructuring Meeting, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Woodbridge Fellows, 2013-2014 (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - Worker Rights Consortium - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 62)
    - World Fellows Program - Dinner and Ceremony, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 63)
    - World Fellows Program - Director Appointment - Sky, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 64)
    - Woodbridge Fellows - Resumes and Questions, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 65)
    - World Fellows Program - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 66)
    - World Fellows Program - Information Materials, 2002-2015 (Box 30, Folder 67)
    - World Fellows Project - Interviews, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 68)
    - Wye Faculty Seminar - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 69)
    - Yale College - Student Funding Requests, 2012-2013 (Box 30, Folder 70)
    - Yale: A Short History - Publication Proofs, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 71)
    - Yale Dance Theater, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 72)
    - Yale DNA - Publication, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 73)
    - Yale Environment Sustainability Summit - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 74)
    - Yale Global Alumni Leadership Exchange, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 75)
    - Yale in Washington Program - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 30, Folder 76)
    - Yale-New Haven community Health Initiative, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 77)
    - Yale-New Haven Educational Programs - Publication, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 78)
    - Yale Program for the Study of Antisemitism, 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 79)
    - Yale Symphony Orchestra - Correspondence and Reports, 2012-2015 (Box 30, Folder 80)
    - Yale University Women's Organization - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 81)
    - Yale Women - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 82)
    - Yalies in Technology - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 83)
    - Young African Leaders at Yale, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 84)
    - Fareed Zakaria - Visit, 2014 February 26 (Box 30, Folder 85)
  - Trip Files
    - Asia, 2013 March 8-2013 March 20 (Box 30, Folder 86)
    - Asia - March - Yale-NUS College, 2015 (Box 30, Folder 87)
    - Atlanta, 2014 May 6 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Beijing, 2015 March 12 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Beijing and Hong Kong, 2015 March 13-2015 March 14 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Berkeley, San Francisco and Menlo Park, California and Owensboro, Kentucky, 2014 June 22-2014 June 29 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Boston, 2013 December 20 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Brazil, 2014 July 26-2014 July 31 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Brazil - Logistics and Briefing Materials - July (folder 1 of 2), 2014 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Brazil - Logistics and Briefing Materials - July (folder 2 of 2), 2014 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - California, 2013 November 10-2013 November 12 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - China, 2013 April 12-2013 April 17 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - China - President Salovey in China-Compact Disc PS, 2014 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - China, 2014 March 19 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - China (folder 1 of 2), 2014 March 26-2014 March 29 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - China (folder 2 of 2), 2014 March 26-2014 March 29 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Cincinnati, Ohio, 2014 September 20 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Davos - World Economic Forum, 2014 January 18-2014 January 27 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Davos - World Economic Forum, 2015 January 18-2015 January 24 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Davos - World Economic Forum - Annual Meeting, 2014 January 14-2015 January 21 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Denver, 2014 November 13 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Fairfield and New York City, 2013 October 28-2013 October 29 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Far Hills, New Jersey, 2013 December 3 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Florida, 2015 January 11-2015 January 14 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Fort Worth and Houston, Texas, 2014 February 9-2014 February 10 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Greenwich, 2013 December 2 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Hamptons, 2013 August 2-2013 August 3 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Hong Kong, 2014 March 16-2014 March 18 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Houston and Fort Worth, Texas, 2014 December 16-2014 December 17 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Kentucky and Minnesota, 2015 April 25-2015 April 28 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - London, 2014 January 18-2014 January 21 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - London and Davos, 2015 January 18-2015 January 24 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Menlo Park and San Francisco, California, 2015 June 21-2015 June 25 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Minneapolis and Boston, 2014 June 16-2014 June 18 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Moscow, 2014 February 3-2014 February 5 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Nashville, Tennesee, 2015 March 15-2015 March 17 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - New Jersey, 2013 November 15-2013 November 16 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - New York City, 2013 February 11 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - New York City, 2013 August 13 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - New York City, 2013 September 3 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - New York City, 2013 September 16 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - New York City, 2013 November 5 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - New York City, 2013 November 20 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - New York City, 2013 November 22 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - New York City, 2013 December 17 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - New York City, 2014 January 6-2014 January 7 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - New York City, 2014 April 1 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - New York City, 2014 April 16 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - New York City, 2014 May 22 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - New York City, 2014 June 2-2014 June 3 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - New York City, 2014 June 10-2014 June 11 (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - New York City, 2014 September 3 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - New York City, 2014 August 26 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - New York City, 2014 September 18 (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - New York City, 2014 September 22-2014 September 23 (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - New York City, 2014 October 15 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - New York City, 2014 October 23 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - New York City, 2014 December 5-2014 December 9 (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - New York City, 2015 February 23 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - New York City, 2015 March 2 (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - New York City, 2015 June 1-2015 June 2 (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - New York City, 2015 June 16-2015 June 17 (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - New York City and Fort Worth, Texas, 2015 31 March-2015 April 1 (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - New York City and Memphis, Tennessee, 2015 May 3-2015 May 5 (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - New York City and Washington, DC, 2013 December 10-2013 December 11 (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - Owensboro and Louisville, Kentucky and Minneapolis, Minnesota, 2015 April 18-2015 April 25 (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - Owensboro, Kentucky and Washington, D.C., 2014 April 25-2014 April 29 (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Paris and London, 2013 January 18-2013 January 22 (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - Philadelphia, 2013 December 16 (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - San Francisco, 2015 February 1-2015 February 4 (Box 31, Folder 68)
    - San Francisco and Menlo Park, California, 2014 June 24-2014 June 25 (Box 31, Folder 69)
    - Singapore, 2014 September 8-2014 September 9 (Box 31, Folder 70)
    - Singapore, 2013 September 23-2013 September 25 (Box 31, Folder 71)
    - Singapore and Beijing, 2015 March 6-2015 March 13 (Box 31, Folder 72)
    - Singapore and China, 2014 March 7-2014 March 14 (Box 31, Folder 73)
    - Trumbull, Connecticut and New York City, 2014 May 22 (Box 31, Folder 74)
    - Vero Beach and Miami, Florida, 2015 January 11-2015 January 14 (Box 31, Folder 75)
    - Washington, DC, 2013 January 24-2013 January 25 (Box 31, Folder 76)
    - Washington, DC, 2013 October 20-2013 October 22 (Box 31, Folder 77)
    - Washington, DC, 2013 December 8 (Box 31, Folder 78)
    - Washington, DC, 2014 January 15-2014 January 17 (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Washington, DC, 2014 July 23-2014 July 24 (Box 31, Folder 80)
    - Washington, DC, 2014 August 8-2014 August 11 (Box 31, Folder 81)
    - Washington, DC, 2014 September 30-2014 October 1 (Box 31, Folder 82)
    - Washington, DC, 2014 October 19-2014 October 21 (Box 31, Folder 83)
    - Washington, DC, 2015 April 10-2015 April 21 (Box 31, Folder 84)
    - West Palm Beach, Florida and Moscow, 2014 February 2-2014 February 5 (Box 31, Folder 85)
    - Westport, Connecticut and New York City, 2014 April 8 (Box 31, Folder 86)